仅供学习 禁止用于任何商业盈利行为
更多影视更新
请登陆www.ZiMuZu.tv
原创翻译  双语字幕
翻译:  小笼包    亲爱的小饭
翻译:  芝小士    吃货丁小七
校对:  慕容龙飞
时间轴:  浓子
后期:  瓜瓜2016版    总监： 瓜瓜
打开微信   扫描左侧二维码
或搜索公众号:    美剧炸了
了解最新影视资讯字幕信息
摩  登
家  庭
第七季 第二十二集
最新美剧下载
www.ZiMuZu.tv
克莱尔  卢克床上有个女孩
Claire. There's a girl in Luke's bed.
卢克在哪儿
Where's Luke?
跟女孩在一起啊
With the girl!
我们该制造点噪音把她吓走吗
Should we just make a noise and scare her off?
是女孩还是负鼠
Is it a girl or a possum?
亲爱的  根本没人
Honey, there's no one there.
刚刚有的  我看到了一个女孩  还有头发
There was. I saw girl bumps and hair.
可能只是他的丘巴卡娃娃
It was probably just his Chewbacca doll.
不是娃娃  那是个毛绒动作玩偶
It's not a doll. It's a plush action figure.
只要他还跟那玩意儿一起睡
Well, as long as he's sleeping with that thing,
它就只会有陪睡这个动作
it's the only action he's gettin'.
我真是松了口气  我还没准备好他那样呢
I'm so relieved. I wasn't ready for that.
你以为你看到了根本不存在的东西
You thought you saw something that wasn't there.
很黑  我们还一起喝了一整瓶酒
It's dark, and we shared an entire bottle of wine.
确实黑
It is dark.
我都没看到你说"一起"时那种开玩笑的样子
I didn't see you do air quotes around "shared".
好吧  这些合同都没问题了
All right. These contracts are good to go.
只剩下检查了
All that's left is the inspection.
已经安排好了
Already scheduled it.
安迪  如果我能把你塞进一瓶古龙水里
Andy, if I could bottle you up
然后封起来  你知道我会把你命名为什么吗
and put you into a cologne, you know what I'd call it?
进取号
"Initiative."
黑白广告
The black-and-white commercial
会让模特都变成黑豹
would have models turning into panthers.
进取号  来自加州的中性香水
"Initiative -- a unisex fragrance from California."
尽管我想继续跟你打趣
I want to come back to this because it's fun,
但我需要你的建议
but I need your advice.
你还记得我在犹他州的堂兄吗
You remember my cousin back in Utah,
-那个房地产开发商  -记得啊
- the real-estate developer? - Yeah.
他的副总要辞职
Well, turns out his V.P.'s leaving
去自己开公司了
to start his own company,
然后我堂兄需要人接替他  现在就要...
and my cousin needs someone, like -- like, now.
那是个很不错的机...
That's a big opp--
你怎么回来了
What are you doing home?
你开玩笑吗  放假了啊  我回家过暑假啊
Are you serious? School's out. I'm home for the summer.
你知道的
You knew this.
我一定是走神了  我好开心你回来了
Must have slipped my mind. I'm so glad you're back.
就这样了吗
That's it?
桑杰的父母给他搞了个
Sanjay's parents are throwing him
三天的"欢迎回家"派对
a three-day "Welcome Home" party.
他们甚至用金盏花给他做了一套西服
They even made him a suit out of marigolds.
真是惊喜啊  小宝贝
This is a nice surprise, pumpkin.
是我在日历上
Was I too subtle with the way
艾娘娘回宫啦  接驾
写得还不明显  还是...
I put it on the calendar, or...
某人起床心情很好哟
Someone woke up in a good mood.
一个少年会这样子
And there is only one reason
只有一个原因
a teenage boy is ever like that.
是啊  因为今天是家庭露营训练日
Yep, because it's Family Camp training day!
我本来想说
Oh, I was gonna say,
一定是哈林篮球队来了
"The Harlem Globetrotters must be in town."
卢克和我正在为很重要家庭十项全能做训练
Luke and I are training for the big...Famcathlon.
你吃得...真不少啊
You're, uh, carb-loading.
好主意  哥们
Good idea, buddy!
挺饿[饥渴]呀
Hungry dude.
渴望家庭露营
Hungry for Family Camp!
别马上拒绝我  快想象一下我打扮成这样
Don't say "No" right away, but picture me with these.
亲爱的  你才八岁  你的身体还需要时间成长
Sweetie, you're 8 years old. Give your body time to develop.
这卷发  我想要烫头发
These curls! I want a perm!
你去看看你的同龄人
Take it from someone
谁有烫头发的  你找不到的
who had a perm at your age -- you don't.
好了  你觉得我穿这身儿上飞机怎么样
Okay, what do you think of my airplane outfit?
我降落在密苏里的时候  我想马上融入其中
When I land in Missouri, I want to blend right in.
融入什么  坛罐乐队吗
With what? A jug band?
我今年夏天找到了一份工作
I got a job this summer
去密苏里州橄榄球队
as an assistant defensive coordinator
当助理防守教练
for the Missouri State football team.
我要回家啦
Go, Bears! I'm going home.
我最近工作又非常忙  这意味着
And I have been crazy with work, which means
莉莉得在我们俩之间来回跑
Lily will be going back and forth between the two of us.
不过我们俩在商量
It has been a little tense
时间安排的时候  有点小紧张
putting together a time-share agreement, though.
我可没有故意制造紧张
I haven't been making it tense.
是你把我们女儿
You're the one who treats our daughter
当成个阿鲁巴的度假房产似的
like she's a vacation property in Aruba.
也许应该提拔你做个超强防守[爱还口的]教练
Maybe you should be promoted to very defensive coordinator.
-给你  -你打出了
- There you go. - Okay, you typed up
我们要怎么分享我们的女儿
how we're gonna share our daughter.
这是什么  监护协议吗
What is this -- some sort of custody agreement?
我起草了一份文件
I just drafted a document
内容大致是我们昨晚商量的东西
that reflects what we discussed last night.
你老是忘记你同意了的事情啊  小卡
You have a tendency to forget about things you agreed to, Cam.
那真是胡说八道
Okay, that's a bunch of hooey.
里奇  我忘记拿毛巾了  说明不了什么
Rich! I forgot to bring up the towels. That proves nothing.
我本不想打扰你  但我去法庭快迟到了
I wouldn't bother you, but I'm late for court.
非常清楚直白
It's really very straightforward.
如果密苏里连下超过三天的雨
If it rains for more than three days in Missouri,
我的时间就抵掉一些
that borrows against my time.
相反  如果莉莉去了体操营
Conversely, if Lily does go to gymnastics camp,
就要多给我一周
I get an extra week.
太难懂了
It's too confusing.
等等  你是律师  对吧
Wait -- You're a lawyer, right?
我能请你帮我看个东西吗
Can I actually have you take a peek at something for me?
你要干什么
W-What are you doing?
我在请律师呢
I'm lawyering up.
是啊
uh, yeah.
这份合同里有太多模糊用语了
There's a lot of ambiguous language in this contract.
我要是你就不会签的
I wouldn't sign it.
没人让他签啊
Nobody's asking him to.
我永远不会同意放弃国庆日那天陪莉莉的
You know, I never would have agreed to give up 4th of July,
现在我都担心
and now I'm worried
他在骗我放弃在好运饼干日那天陪莉莉的权力
he's trying to trick me out of Biscuit Bonanza.
好运饼干日
B-Biscuit Bonanza?
就是你听到的这样
It's what it sounds like.
是一个饼干烘焙比赛
It's a biscuit-baking competition,
比看看谁能把自己的饼干扔得最远
and then you see who can throw theirs the furthest.
我能展示一下证据A吗
May I present Exhibit "A"?
没关系  米奇尔  我才不在意国庆日
That's fine, Mitchell -- I don't care about 4th of July,
只要我能带莉莉参加好运饼干日
as long as I get Lily for Biscuit Bonanza.
好运饼干
Biscuit Bonanza?!
对  就是你听到的这样  是一个饼干烘焙...
Yeah. It's what it sounds like. It's a biscuit-baking --
算了  我从来没这么讨厌过我的声音
Okay, I have never hated the sound of my own voice more.
好  我要去挑衣服了
Okay. I'm gonna go pick up that costume.
什么  衣服  天呐  小卡
What costume? Oh, my God, Cam.
别忘了和胡娇吃早午餐
Don't forget about Pepper's brunch.
好  够了
Okay, stop it!
今天不是你第一天回去和克莱尔工作吗
Isn't it your first day back working with Claire?
我得先把这封邮件
I got to get this e-mail out first
发到那家搞错我订单的店里去
to a store that got my order wrong.
我看着像那种
Do I look like a guy
会穿一件全是菠萝的衬衫的家伙吗
who would wear a shirt with pineapples all over it?
有点
Kinda.
我想全用大写字母来显示我有多么生气
I want to use all caps to get across how angry I am,
但是输入每个字目前都按一次"Shift"键实在太慢了
but it takes forever to press "Shift" before each letter.
你为什么直接锁定大写
Why don't you just put on the caps lock?
可以这样吗
You can do that?
杰
Oh, Jay.
双击这里
Just double-click here.
不管用
Didn't work.
那是因为你没有双击
Well, that's because you didn't double-click.
你只是点击了两次
You just clicked twice.
有什么区别吗
The hell's the difference?
双击  看到没
Double-click. See?
我就是这样啊
That's exactly what I did.
双...击
Double...click.
不对  你只是点击了两次
No, you're still just clicking twice.
听我说  双击
Listen to me -- "Double-click."
不是  双...击
Not "Double...click."
我不是傻子
I'm not an idiot.
双击
Double-click!
这怎么可能是一样的
You can't possibly think that's the same thing!
那就是完全一样的
It's the exact same thing!
双击
Double-click!
我...
Oh, what the...
这是我第一次说那个艹字头的字
It's the first time I've ever used the F-word.
发生什么事了
Ay, what's going on here?
连我都觉得你们在尖叫
Even for me, it's a little screamy!
我要去工作了
I'm going to work! Wh--
你怎么把他惹生气了
Why did you get him so mad?
我需要他有个好心情
I need him in a good mood.
我还得叫他下周跟我
I need to ask him to go with me next week
去华雷斯参加我表弟的婚礼呢
to Juárez to my cousin's wedding.
那里安全吗
Is that safe?
当然不
Of course not.
邀请函上写着  请快速跑到接待处
The invitation says "Short run to the reception".
万一泊车小弟因为我手短
What are the odds the valet slid the seat back
故意把椅子往后调怎么办
because of my weirdly short arms?
该死  我得接这个电话
Shoot. I should take this.
那钱包就给我了
Then I... should take this.
埃文
Evan.
我知道你为什么打给我
Look, I know why you're calling,
不  我没有改变主意
and no, I haven't changed my mind.
我不想接受这份工作
I still don't want the job.
所以你拒绝这么好的机会
So, you're turning down a chance
不肯回家乡接受这么棒一份工作
to move home for your dream job --
不愿开始自己的事业  就因为一个女的吗
an actual career -- all because of a girl?
这个叫海莉的一定很特别
This Haley must be something special.
喂
Hello?
信号好像断了
I think I lost you.
喂  埃文
Hello? Evan?
我挂了  回头再给他打
Dropped call. I'll try him back.
我就知道会这样
I knew it!
谢谢
Thanks.
欢迎回来  杰
Good to have you back, Jay!
回来真好  哥们儿
Good to be back, buddy.
公司沟通小技巧
Little trick of the trade --
当你不记得某人名字的时候  就叫他哥们儿
when you don't know somebody's name, you call 'em "Buddy".
办公室还是老样子
So, the old office, huh?
你把灯放到那边去了
I see you got the lamp over there now.
我这么做过一次
I tried it there once.
你会知道结果的
You'll see.
你的办公室下午就能收拾好
Your office is gonna be ready this afternoon.
你要去拿新的...
Do you want to go pick up your new --
所以现在在忙什么  季度报告吗
So, what are we working on? Quarterly reports?
其实不是  这是人事文件
Actually, no. This is a personnel file.
我今天得炒了尼尔
I have to fire Neal today.
-尼尔  -对  尼尔
- Neal? - Yeah -- Neal.
在库房工作  喜欢加拿大那个胖乎乎的家伙
Works in the warehouse, loves Canada, heavyset fella.
你是说大哥们儿啊
Oh, you mean "Big Buddy".
他犯错造成的损失比我们靠他赚的还多
We are losing more in shipping screw-ups than he makes.
是时候了
It's time.
-你现在就要去吗  -不是
- You gonna do that now? - Oh. No.
其实我现在要去复印
Um, actually, right now, I was going to make copies
今天下午员工会议的安排
of the agenda for this afternoon's staff meeting.
我来吧  你要多少份
Let me do it. How many do you need?
12份双面打印
Uh, 12 double-sided --
爸  你确定要去吗
Dad, are you sure?
你知道复印室在哪吗
Do you even know where the copy room is?
克莱尔  拜托  这地方就是我建的
Claire. Please. I built this place.
好吧
Okay.
另一边
Other way.
-你好  杰  -晚点再说  哥们儿
- Hi, Jay. - Not now, buddy!
"哥们儿"策略对我爸可能有用
That "Buddy" stuff may have worked for my dad,
但我想要建立一种更私人的联系
but I wanted a more personal touch when I took over.
我希望大家能够开心地工作
I wanted this to be a fun place to work,
所以我在库房安了一台跳舞机
so I had an arcade dance game installed in the warehouse.
我觉得你稍微给他们一点甜头
I figure you give them a little sugar,
能够减轻炒掉人的消极影响
takes the edge off when you have to fire someone like...
发生什么事了
What is going on?
尼尔简直是为跳舞机而生的
Dude, Neal is tearing it up on this dance machine.
你看他的分数
Check out his score.
他动作相当快
He's pretty quick on that thing.
别担心  克莱尔
Oh, don't worry, Claire.
他肯定不可能打破你的记录
He's never gonna beat your record.
你的记录已经保持几个月了  无人能及
You've had that for months. No one's even come close.
我一点都不担心那个
Oh, I'm not worried about that.
好吧  戒备心别这么强嘛
Okay. God. Don't be defensive.
新纪录
New high score!
我成功了
I did it!
新纪录
New high score!
抱歉  克莱尔
Uh, s-sorry, Claire.
我可不想当破了老板记录的人
Yikes. I would not want to be the guy who just beat the boss.
我挺喜欢这份工作的
I actually like my job.
能帮我拉一下拉链吗
Hey, can I get a zip?
我要买这件
I'm gonna take it.
胡娇的派对很有趣却也令人费解
Pepper's parties are as fun as they are confusing.
仔细听我接下来说的
Okay, stay with me on this one.
百老汇性别错乱早午餐
Gender Blender Broadway Brunch.
你化妆成跟自己性别相反的百老汇角色
You dress as a Broadway character of the opposite sex,
而且派对不提供固体食物
and there's no solid food.
对于下巴脱臼的
It's a perfect party
舞会皇后来说这个派对十分完美
if you're a show queen with a broken jaw.
不好意思
Uh, excuse me.
抱歉  普里契特先生  你的卡刷不了
Sorry, Mr. Pritchett. Your card has been declined.
不可能吧
Oh, no, that's impossible.
不  我试了三次了
No, I ran it, like, three times.
我貌似应该把卡剪掉
I think I'm supposed to cut it.
不要剪  我车里有现金
Oh, no, no! Don't cut it! I have some cash in the car.
你能帮我拉开拉链吗  好像卡住了
Can you just unzip me? I think it's stuck.
是卡住了  你要我剪开它吗
Oh, it is stuck. You want me to cut it?
不要  不要剪
No, no! Don't cut it!
天呐  你怎么那么想剪东西
God. You really want to cut something.
我马上回来
I'll be right back.
该死
Oh, damn it!
不好意思  跟你合影多少钱
Excuse me. How much for a picture?
我其实不是...
Oh, I'm actually not --
拜托了  我们女儿超爱"红发安妮"
Please. Our daughter loves "Annie".
好吧
Well, uh...
我收大概20刀吧
actually, I-I could use, like, $20.
20刀  金刚狼才收10刀
$20? Wolverine was $10.
我不想跟你吵  我只是需要...
Look, I don't want to fight. I just -- I just need --
喂  你砸场子呢
Hey, man. What the hell?
不是吧
No, no, no!
想让杰按我的想法做事很不容易
It's not easy to get Jay to do what I want,
所以有时候我得用上我的秘密武器
so sometimes I have to use my secret weapon.
不过当我懒得用秘密武器的时候
But when I'm too tired for that,
我会给他放催泪电影
I just play one of the movies that make him cry like a baby.
这是《追梦赤子心》吗
Is this "Rudy"?
我超爱这电影
Oh, I love this movie.
是吗
You do?
杰  我买了两张芭蕾舞的票
Jay, I got us tickets to the ballet,
可是我知道你周日要去打高尔夫
but I know that you're golfing on Sunday.
我都听你的
Whatever you want.
鲁迪虽然是个小人物
You know, Rudy was small,
他的心胸却很宽广
but he had a big heart.
乔  这些卡通都是什么
Joe, what are all these cartoons?
妈咪的电影都没有了
Now all of Mommy's movies are gone!
是曼尼做的
Manny did it.
我照顾这小家伙的时候该怎么做
What am I supposed to do when I babysit this guy?
跟他说话吗
Make conversation?
这孩子只会讲两个故事
The kid has two stories.
看  我是一棵树
Look. I'm a tree.
这还算是比较好的故事
That's the good one.
普里契特橱柜公司
妈  你为什么不回我电话
Mom, why aren't you calling me back?
我在你公司  我有话跟你说
I'm at your work. I need to talk.
不好意思  你见到克莱尔了吗
Uh, excuse me. Have you seen Claire?
有人说她在下面
Someone said she was down here.
没有
Uh, nope.
我炒不了尼尔
I couldn't fire Neal.
人家会觉得我炒他
It would look like I was only doing it
都是因为他破了我的记录
to get back at him for beating my record.
游戏结束
Game over!
所以我别无选择  必须先破了尼尔的记录
So I had no choice -- I had to beat Neal's score.
喂
Hello?
复印机要怎么用啊
How do you work a copy machine?
你不是吧
You can't be serious.
我需要双面复印12份文件
I need to make 12 double-sided copies.
这是个不可能完成的任务
It's an impossible task.
你就不能找个人帮忙吗
Can't you just ask someone for help?
我大张旗鼓地回来上班
I made a big deal out of coming back here to work.
得表现出自己有用
I'd like to appear useful.
等等  屏幕上有个感叹号
Wait -- On the screen, there's an exclamation mark.
是不是好兆头
Is that good?
它应该不是因为当前状况而激动
I don't think it means it's excited about what's happening.
你有把原件放到托盘里吗
Did you put the original in the tray?
托盘  像上菜的托盘那种吗
Tray? You mean like a serving tray?
对的  杰  把纸放到上菜的托盘里
Yes, Jay. I want you to put papers in a serving tray.
你是怎么苟活至今的
How have you remained alive?
我找到了
I found it!
好  好
Yeah! Yeah!
简直了  卡纸了
Great! It's stuck!
没关系  千万别硬拉...
That's okay. Whatever you do, don't pull the --
等等  我把纸拉出来
Hold on. I'm pulling it.
不
No!
有了  新最高分  终于
Yes! New high score! Finally!
饿了吗
Are you hungry?
怎么了  又是惠特尼·休斯顿诞辰吗
What's wrong? Is it Whitney Houston's birthday again?
不是  亲爱的  我只是因为
No, honey, I'm just sad about
要离开你那么久而伤心
being away from you for so long.
我们还能在一起度过六小时
We still have six hours together.
咱们来过特别的一天吧
Let's have a special day!
肯定很有意思
Oh, that would be fun.
我们可以去骑车或者野餐
We could take a bike ride or have a picnic.
我在想更持久的东西
I was thinking something a little more permanent.
好了  准备接橘子
Okay. Prepare to receive.
记住  关键就在靠在一起的力量
And remember, it's all about the strength of the nestle.
他脖子上有很小但清晰可见的红印
A tiny but noticeable red mark on his neck?
我不傻
I'm not an idiot.
某人一直在自己练接橘子
Someone's been practicing his orange grip.
跟上脚步
Pick up the pace!
我们要靠这个弥补
This is where we make up
你妈妈在呼啦圈的劣势
for your mom being so bad at Hula-Hooping.
走你
Shoot!
我在卢克的窗子下偶然发现了这个
I randomly found this in a bush under Luke's window.
可能是艾丽克斯找海莉借来穿
Alex probably asked Haley to borrow them,
海莉扔了这双鞋
Haley threw the pair,
艾丽克斯接到一只
Alex caught one,
另一只从窗户飞了出来
the other one flew out the window,
电话响了  她们就忘了  女孩子啊
phone call came, they forgot. Girls.
你在家干什么
What are you doing home?
接受家人一次又一次的打击
Being crushed over and over by family members.
收到你短信了
Got your message.
我知道你的意思可能不是"马上来"
I know you probably didn't mean "Come over right away,"
不过你知道我挺偏执的  所以
but you know how paranoidy I can be, so...
去我屋里谈吧
We should talk in my room.
好的
O...kay.
安迪  等等
Andy. Hold on a sec.
我知道我们刚才没谈完
I know we didn't get to finish our talk earlier,
因为艾丽克斯忽然出现
because of Alex's surprise pop-in.
听着
Listen.
如果你不接受犹他州的那份工作是因为我
If you're not taking that job in Utah because of me,
那你就错了
you're making a mistake.
我喜欢咱们在一起  但如果你因为我
I love you and me together, but it would break my heart
放弃这个梦想的职位
if I was the reason
我会很伤心的
you gave up this dream career opportunity,
因为  说实话
because, honestly,
我不知道这里有多少未来
I don't know how much of a future there is here.
不过
But...
如果我们的联系真有我想的那么紧密
if our bond is as strong as we think it is...
我们会想办法回到对方身边的
we'll work our way back to each other.
好的
Okay.
他说的就是我想说的
What he said.
你们聊什么呢
Hey, what's all the buzz about?
终于有人超过尼尔无法超越的...
Somebody finally top Neal's untoppable --
怎么回事
What happened?
有人把跳舞机电源拔了
Someone unplugged the dance machine.
所以我的最高分没了
So my high score's gone?
是尼尔的最高分吧
Don't you mean Neal's high score?
不是  我得了805分  大概20分钟前
No! I got an 805, like, 20 minutes ago!
不是吧
Oh, come on!
你们不会认为我有那么生气
Y-You can't think that I'm really so upset
真的把...
that I would actually --
天呐  克莱尔
Damn, Claire.
你没必要这样阴人家吧
You didn't have to go all "Black Swan" on the guy.
我们难道就这么不信任她吗
Are we really not believing this woman?
她始终对我们很坦诚
She's never been anything but honest with us.
我搞砸事情的时候  她都会告诉我
When I screw up, she lets me know it,
用很体贴的方式
but in a caring way.
对你也是  本纳德  汤姆
Same with you, Bernard...Tom.
马利  你懂的
Marie, you know it.
我们应该感谢她
It's time we started appreciating this lady.
她可能在跳舞游戏上得了800分
She may have gotten an 800 on the dance game,
如果你们问我的话
but if you ask me,
她在当老板游戏里得了1000分
she gets a 1,000 on the boss game.
好吧
Okeydoke.
衣服拿了吗
Did you get the costumes?
差点拿不了  信用卡没法刷
Barely. My credit card was denied,
某人又把车里所有现金花光了
and someone spent all the cash we had in the car.
对  都是我的错  我道歉
Uh, yeah. Those are probably both on me. I-I apologize.
咱们把我今天做的所有事抛到脑后吧
Let's maybe just forgive everything I've done today.
"所有事"  什么意思
"Everything"? What does that mean?
就是这个意思
It means this!
我的天
Ohhh, my God!
我只是想在走之前给她一份特别的礼物
I just wanted to give her a special treat before I left.
咱们不是说好要等她再大点吗
I thought we were gonna wait until she was older.
我是不是该把这个也写到协议里
Did I have to put that in writing, too?
我能不能告他  我想告他
Can I sue him? I want to sue him.
你们都有充分的理由生我气
You both have every right to be upset with me.
也许离开我几周是件好事
And maybe a few weeks away from me will do some good.
我打车去机场
I'm just gonna get a cab to the airport.
别小家子气了  我们开车送你去
Don't be crazy. We'll drive you.
不用了  我受不了在大庭广众下伤感的告别
No, I don't think I can handle a public emotional goodbye!
还记得这个可人儿吗
Remember her?
我去
Damn it!
爸
Dad?
日程表在我这  克莱尔
Of course I have the agendas, Claire.
我只是想  证明一点
I was just... trying to prove a point.
我是说  那些日程表有什么用
I mean, what do you need those things for, anyway?
日程表  就像拐棍  弱者才用
Agendas -- they're crutches. They're for the weak.
你以为开国元老会用这种东西吗
You think the founding fathers wrote down an agenda?
说的不就是独立宣...
Well, isn't the Declaration of Inde--
领导人就该领导  不是读稿
A leader leads, not reads.
拿着一叠日程表去开会
You go into that meeting with a bunch of agendas,
就是在寻求他们的认同
you're asking for their approval.
喜欢我吧  喜欢我吧  喜欢我吧
"Like me! Like me! Like me!"
我就不喜欢
I say "No"!
我跟你说过多少次
How many times have I told you --
当好老板的第一条规则就是
the first rule of being a good boss is
不要让员工成为你的朋友
"You don't need your employees to be your friends."
要让他们尊重你
You need them to respect you!
谢谢
Thank you.
我需要听的正是这些话
That is...exactly what I needed to hear.
-分内之事而已  -对
- I'm just doing my job. - Yeah.
相信自己  孩子
Just trust your gut, kid.
双击
Double-click...
自己
on...yourself.
什么这么香
What smells so good?
为我自己的"欢迎回家"大餐
I'm making my favorite lasagna
做我最喜欢的意大利千层面
for my own "Welcome Home" dinner.
能不能问你个事
Can I ask you a question?
-什么事  -你觉得你弟
- What? - Do you think it's possible
有没有可能在昨晚偷偷带女孩子回家
that your brother snuck a girl in here last night?
我不会那么惊讶
I wouldn't be too surprised.
所以你觉得他  他们已经
So you think he's -- t-that they've been --
得了吧  爸  别那么天真
Oh, come on, Dad. Don't be so naive.
谁都有过十七年华
We were all 17 once.
说得好像谁还是...
It's not like we all --
我在那坐了有20分钟
I sat there like that for 20 minutes.
然后又听到了更可怕的消息
And then I got some more awful news.
我刚收到邮件说家庭露营活动取消了
I just got an e-mail saying Family Camp was canceled --
报名人数不够
not enough sign-ups.
就这样吗
That's it?
你一点都不关心  是不是
You don't care at all, do you?
忙着跟昨晚那个姑娘缠缠绵绵
You're too busy running around with that girl from last night!
对  没错  我什么都知道
Yeah! That's right! I know everything!
你怎么能这样呢  卢克
How could you, Luke?
其实我不知道自己为什么这么生气
To be honest, I don't know why I was so upset.
我知道我是该生气
I knew I was supposed to be mad,
但我说不出具体原因
but I couldn't figure out why,
所以我只能照套路先说他几句
so I just started saying a bunch of stuff.
就在我家
Under my roof?!
这句好诡异
That was weird.
在我付钱买的床上
In a bed that I paid for?!
说这话意义何在
What does that have to do with anything?
就在你爷爷的眼皮底下
With your grandfather watching?!
意义何在
What?
但这都远不够我真正想说的那么夸张
But it wasn't half as crazy as what I really wanted to yell,
那就是  "别再长大了"
which was "Just stop growing up!"
听着  我不保证我现在说的全部有道理
Look, I'm not sure everything I said here makes sense,
但是你真得谨慎点  有点敬畏心
but...just be careful and respectful.
而且你的确犯了一个大错
And you did break a big rule,
罚你一个月不准用家里的车
so no car privileges for a month.
我也用不着车了
I don't need it anyway.
我被人甩了
I just got dumped.
我们就那样在那里坐了20分钟
We sat there like that for 20 minutes.
第一天上班怎么样
How was your first day at work?
有点小困难
It was a little rough,
但我好像也惹了点麻烦
but I kind of stumbled into something.
妈咪你不是要问他吗
Aren't you going to ask him, Mommy?
他在说什么
What's he talking about?
没什么
Nothing.
我本来想叫你下礼拜陪我去华雷斯
I was going to ask you to go to Juárez with me
参加我表亲婚礼的
next week for my cousin's wedding,
但我知道你肯定不愿意  所以我自己去
but I know that you don't want to go, so I'll go alone.
你真的不去吗
You're really not gonna go?
你也听见她说了  她自己去没事
Well, you heard her. She's fine going alone.
如果飞机落地的时候是她一个人出舱
If that plane leaves the ground and you're not with her,
你一定会后悔的
you'll regret it.
也许今天明天你没有感觉
Maybe not today and maybe not tomorrow,
但很快你就会后悔  而且会后悔一辈子
but soon, and for the rest of your life.
你在说什么  《卡萨布兰卡》的台词吗
What did you say? Is that "Casablanca"?
《卡萨布兰卡》中的经典台词
"不难看清  在这纷纷乱世"
"It doesn't take much to see"
"三个小人物的问题"
"the problems of three little people"
"其实无足轻重"
"don't amount to a hill of beans in this crazy world."
"总有一天你会明白的"
"Someday, you'll understand that."
"好了  没事了"
"Now, now."
"没事的  孩子"
Here's looking at you, kid.
歌洛莉亚  关于那场婚礼
Gloria! About that wedding --
我已经在订机票了
I'm already booking the ticket!
好  它长出来了
Okay, it's growing!
我在跟信用卡公司打电话
I'm on hold with the credit-card company.
我们要不找找看今晚吃什么
We should probably try and figure out dinner.
我连冰箱里有什么都不知--
I have no idea what we even have in the --
天呐  莉莉你看
Oh, my God. Lily, look.
大爸给我们做了这么多吃的
Daddy made us all this food.
"加热20分钟  余生都要爱我"
"Heat for 20 minutes. Love me for the rest of time."
旭日东升塔马利[墨西哥玉米粉蒸肉]
"The sun will come out tamales."
天呐
Oh, my God.
你觉得他是不是在忙着做饭
You think he forgot about my curlers
所以忘了帮我摘掉卷发夹
because he was too busy cooking?
可能是吧  我不知--
Maybe. I don't kn--
是的  你好
Oh, yes. Hello?
好--  好的  谢谢
Oka-- Okay. Well, thank you.
大爸买了一张机票
Um, Daddy bought a plane ticket
准备在国庆日给我们一个惊喜
to surprise us on the 4th of July.
所以我的信用卡才透支了
That's why my credit card was over the limit.
我好后悔当时冲着他那样喊
Now I feel bad for yelling at him.
是  我也后悔了
Yeah, me too.
到达大厅  出发大厅
那么  到这儿就该结束了[队尾]
So, this is the end of the line.
不  不是  我跟你说过的
No. No! I told you!
你会来看我  我也会去看--
You're gonna come visit, I'll come there --
不是  我说的是安检队伍
No. I meant security.
那我们...  不来那些煽情的套路了
So... none of that messy stuff,
又不是要永别
because this is not goodbye goodbye.
对  离别不舍的戏还是留给那边二位吧
Yeah. We'll leave the drama to those two.
"亲爱的  答应我永远不要忘记我"
"Promise me you won't forget me, my darling."
"我会的  除非这老土套装重领时尚"
"I'll love you until this pantsuit comes back in style."
"我不后悔与你度过的每分每秒"
"I don't regret a single minute I've spent with you."
"我觉得你是我真心爱过的第一个男人"
"I think you're the first man I've ever loved."
每分每秒  从不后悔
Not a single minute.
你真的是第一个
You really are the first.
在我成长的过程中  有猪和牛的陪伴
Now, I had pigs and cows when I was growing up --
小卡
Cam!
噢我的天  你们来这儿干什么
Oh, my gosh! What are you guys doing here?
我们俩反思了一整天
We spent the whole day thinking about ourselves,
然后意识到...
and then realized...
你一整天也都在关心呵护着我们
you've spent the whole day thinking about us, too.
所以我拿了点东西给你带回密苏里
So I brought you something to take to Missouri.
我要和你一起回去  大爸
I'm coming with you, Daddy!
我的天呐  我能整个夏天都和她在一起
Oh, my gosh! I get to keep her for the whole summer?
-是的  -但你不会想念她吗
- Yeah! - But won't you miss her?
不  不会
No. No.
因为我也要跟你们一起去
Because I'm coming, too!
我的老--  那你的工作怎么办
My good-- well, what about work?
其实我在密苏里也能完成工作
Well, I figure I could work from there,
然后时不时也能飞回来处理事务
and, you know, fly back when I need to.
避暑纳凉时能被新鲜饼干香气围绕挺好的
Think I could use a summer of smelling fresh biscuits --
还有  显然也能扔饼干
and, apparently, throwing them.
看看这是谁觉得自己第一年就有资格参赛
Well, look who thinks he's gonna qualify his first year.
我们要回去做密苏里人了
We're gonna be Missourians!
有时候你会经历
Sometimes, you have one of those days
被众人围绕着
where you are surrounded by people
却仍然觉得十分孤独的时刻
but you still feel pretty lonely.
你只想回到家人身边汲取安慰
All you want to do is go home to the comfort of your family.
但有时即使是家人都无法给你这种安慰
But sometimes, even your family can't give you that comfort.
因为其实他们也会遭遇和你一样的孤独
Because it turns out they've all had one of those days, too.
你只能隐忍地等到这种煎熬结束
All you can do is wait for days like that to be over...
然后你就能好好睡下
so you can go to bed
希望醒来后是美好的一天
and hope you wake up to a better tomorrow.
菲尔
Phil.
菲尔  我好像听到卢克房里有声响
Phil, I think I hear something in Luke's room.
又来
Again?
怎么了
What?
我们知道你有多喜欢家庭露营训练日
We know how much you love Family Camp.
但是它被取消了
But it was canceled,
我也觉得你们都早就对它无爱了
and I thought you were all kind of over it.
我们可能对它无爱  但是我们爱着彼此
We may be over it, but we're not over us.
你觉得要不要办个升级版家庭露营训练日
What do you think about Family Camp 2.0?
对啊  菲尔  赶紧的  车马上就要到了
Yeah, Phil, come on. Cab's gonna be here any minute.
你不用收拾点行李吗
Don't you have some packing to do?
为什么我们老是要等你
Why are we always waiting on you?
我不知道我收拾完行李要去哪儿
I don't know where I'm packing for,
但是我太高兴了
but I love this!
真棒  这些看上去多美味啊
All right. How good do these look?
所以它们获评"纽约最佳美食"
That's why they call them "New York's Finest."
就是  有美食的陪伴
Yeah, who needs a campfire
没有篝火露营又如何
when we've got a metal box full of gray water?
好了各位  合个影
Okay, everybody, picture.
女士  能帮我们照张相吗
Uh, ma'am? Would you mind?
站到后面去  你这么高  行了行了
get in the back. Get in the back. You're tall. Okay. Okay.
好了  说茄...
All right. And...
现在又少一部手机了
And now we're down to three phones.
老板  是老爸
Hey, boss. It's Dad.
我知道我才刚回来上班
I know I just started back,
但是如果可以  我要请几天假
but I'm taking a couple of days off, if that's okay.
如果不可以也没办法  我在华雷斯
And if not, too bad. I'm in Juárez!
老爸  我是米奇
Hey, Dad. It's Mitch.
那个  我现在和小卡在密苏里
Uh, I'm in Missouri with Cam.
不  我不是被他绑过来的
No, it's not a hostage situation.
您能不能顺路到我们家帮忙浇浇花草
Anyway, uh, can you swing by our place and water our plants?
还有  别忘了卧室里的那盆无花果
Oh, and don't forget about the ficus in the bedroom.
我知道你有多爱到我们卧室里去
I know how much you love to go in there.
我是你姐姐  花姑娘
Hey! It's your big sis, ya big sis.
是这样  我们一家今早飞来纽约了
So, we all flew to New York this morning.
幸好老爸回公司上班  正好替我打掩护
Thank God Dad came back to work. He can cover for me.
无所谓了  对了  我好像没锁后门
Anyway. Listen, I think I left the back door unlocked.
你能帮忙看一下吗
Can you check?
来纽约吧  这里的椒盐脆饼巨大无比
Come to New York! The pretzels are huge!